booked.net 2013-06-28

# Booked.net - About us - Terms & Conditions - Privacy statement

Booked.net is an on-line hotel booking system operated by fast-growing European company Ciliara Trading Limited, which is a private limited liability company, incorporated under the laws of Cyprus.  
We are constantly improving our internet-based service to make it more efficient and to save time for you - our customers.

  * **West European division:**  
Ciliara Trading Limited  
Strovolou 77, Strovolos Center, Office 204  
Strovolos PC 2018 Nicosia, Cyprus  
Phone: +357 220 30 659  
Email: office@ciliara.com  
Website: www.ciliara.com  
Director: Hamervate LTD  
Managing Board: Bogdan Pankiv, Oleksandr Protoven  
Register number: 157423 | VAT ID: CY 10157423i
  * **East European division:**  
Maklai LTD  
Gagarina street #5  
Khmelnitsky 28000, Ukraine  
Phone: +380 44 528 06 79  
Fax: +7 499 503 40 41  
Email: support@booked.net  
Website: www.maklai.com.ua  
Director: Oleksandr Protoven  
Register Number: 35305263

**Service description**  
Booked.net is an on-line hotel booking system operated by fast-growing European company Ciliara Trading Limited, which is a private limited liability company, incorporated under the laws of Cyprus. VAT Number is CY 10157423i. We act as an intermediary between hotels and users. This enables our site users to search and book hotel accommodation online. The hotel descriptions we provide is based on information provided by hotels. Although we do our utmost best to ensure that all information provided on this website is accurate, we cannot guarantee that all information is correct.

The prices on our site are very competitive. All prices on the Booked.net website are per room for your entire stay, unless stated differently. These prices can be changed by the hotels. We show the price we get from the hotel for this room for the dates you select. These are neither rack rates nor competitors' rates. Please check the room details to see what is included in the price and what is not.

**  
Privacy**  
We respect your privacy. We will not give your personal information to third parties under any circumstances. Please have a look at our Privacy Policy for further information.

**  
Credit card guarantee**  
Hotels require credit card details in order to guarantee your reservation. Your credit card information are sent directly to the hotel you reserve. When you make a booking you will automatically enter into an agreement with the hotel you have chosen. Please be assured that some hotels can charge your credit card while booking and some not. So you should check the hotel's policies carefully.  
Be assured that we take our responsibility regarding your credit card information very seriously. We use the industry standard "Secure Socket Layer (SSL)" technology to encrypt your credit card details. Our SSL certificate has been issued by Thawte. Therefore we can guarantee that every transaction made is 100% safe.

**

Cancellation

**  
Please follow the instructions in the confirmation email in case you need to cancel your stay. If you cancel according to the cancellation policy of the hotel, it will be free of charge. We recommend you read the cancellation policy of the hotel carefully. If you cancel later than requested by the hotel or do not show up, the hotel might charge you a fee which is in most cases the equivalent of one night's stay. Note, we don't charge you any cancellation fees whatsoever. But some hotels may charge your credit card. You should check the hotel's policies.

**  
Disclaimer**  
Booked.net has been compiled with the greatest possible care. Our services are based on the information provided by the hotels; for this reason the hotels remain responsible for the correctness of this information. Hotels can alter the information about their hotel, such as prices and availability, at any moment. We can therefore not guarantee that all the information is accurate.

Unless stated otherwise, the copyright of the material on this website is copyright of Booked.net.

**Privacy Policy**  
We take our responsibility regarding your privacy, very seriously. The information we request when making your reservation, is asked for in order to offer you a professional service.  
We only disclose your personal information to third parties for the purposes of completing your booking through us, in order to provide you with the information or services you have requested, with your explicit consent. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information to certain permitted third parties including members of our own group, trusted partners, some of whom are located outside the European Economic Area, and our own professional advisers.

**  
Credit Card information**  
We will not charge your credit card. Your credit card information is only required to guarantee your booking. You pay for your stay at the hotel.  
Your credit card information is sent to us through a secure server. We use the latest, most secure technology available, which encrypts all your personal and credit card details. The encryption method used is the industry standard "Secure Socket Layer" (SSL) technology. Our SSL certificate has been issued by Thawte. 

Our server and network are protected by firewalls against unauthorized access making it totally safe to send us your credit card details.  
Your credit card details will be kept until your arrival date at the hotel. After this date the details will be destroyed.

**  
Control over your data**  
You always have the right to review the personal data you have stored with us. Please state 'request personal data' in the subject line of your email. If your personal data is incorrect, we will change it at your request. You can also ask us to remove your personal data from our database by sending us an email to the same email address.

**  
When do we send you emails?**  
After you have made a booking you will receive a confirmation message with all the information about your booking. You may take this confirmation to the hotel as guarantee of the reservation. Sometimes we may send feedback emails after your stay at the hotel. If you do not wish to give us your opinion, you can let us know and we wil not request any further feedback. In the reservation process you can request our newsletter, which contains special offers and more information sent to your email.   
But, if you no longer wish to receive emails from us, you can simply click on the [unsubscribe](http://booked.net/profile.html) link.

**  
Our contact details**  
Booked.net is an on-line hotel booking system devised by fast-growing European company Ciliara Trading Limited, which is a private limited liability company, incorporated under the laws of Cyprus. VAT Number is CY 10157423i.

If you have any suggestions or remarks about this privacy statement, please send us an email to: [customer.service@Booked.net](mailto:customer.service@Booked.net) or call us at +44 208 144 02 15.
